## Cori Mori

Rochester, NY | 607-794-0354

cori.n.mori@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/cori-mori/ | https://corimori.github.io/client/index.html

# **Game Developer | Gameplay Programming**

Driven Game Developer with 3 years of professional experience in Gameplay Programming. Lead Developer on 5 different small scale projects across 3 years. Assisted in development of 3 other projects in the same span of time. Strives to create scalable, optimized, and immersive gameplay experiences all while developing tools to speed up future development.

#### **Skills**

Game Development | Unreal Engine 5 | Unity | Phaser | C++ | Unreal Blueprints | C# | Javascript | Game Design | Level Design

# **Work Experience**

#### Workinman Interactive | Game Developer

May 2021 - February 2024

- Partnered with the primary development team for Noggin, winner of two Kidscreen awards
- Lead the development of 5 top performing games on the Noggin app
- Collaborated with artists and animators to ensure products met strict brand standards across multiple IPs
- Launched development of advanced features within the Phaser engine, which resulted in an average decrease of 3 days of development time on future projects
- Spearheaded the development of a 3D Phaser engine using ThreeJS and AmmoJS physics

#### Workinman Interactive | Web App Developer

May 2020 - November 2020

- Supported a team of over 10 developers to recreate educational courses from Adobe Flash to HTML
- Lead the development of over 15 modules out of 40 total modules in the span of 7 months
- Utilized Articulate 360 and Javascript to replicate the modules as closely to the original as possible
- Assisted members of the team on their own modules ensure the project was complete by the deadline

#### Magic Spells Studios | Game Designer

January 2020 - May 2020

- Designed a 2D platformer game focusing on movement mechanics featuring original IP
- Collaborated with a developer to ensure design ideas could be replicated in Unity and made adjustments as needed
- Created and implemented 3 platforming levels utilizing the games unique movement mechanics

### **Other Experience**

#### Personal Project | Wizard Wars

March 2024 - Present

- Developed and designed a magical multiplayer experience pitting players against each other in an epic battle of hide and seek in Unreal Engine 5
- Implemented the Gameplay Ability System (GAS) to create a flexible and complex spell casting system utilizing both C++ and Blueprints
- Implemented a client server model for players to seamlessly connect with each other executed using Steam's Advanced Session System

### **Education**

Rochester Institute of Technology | Bachelors of Science | Game Design and Development